This is an automated testing
of your digital phone line.
Sorry, for the interruption
- Charlie
- Victor - Whiskey
- Zero
- Edward
- X
- Lincoln
- Ida
- Alpha
- Frank
Are you awake, mama?
Good morning, angel.
How did you sleep?
Not very well.
I'm sorry.
You ready?
How do you feel?
Not the best.
Slowly. You want some tea?
Gorky
Squeeze my hand.
Good.
Coffee, please.
- Hallo.
- You're late.
Are you in a rush?
Always, I am a busy woman.
Toi, toi my darling.
- You should be back at 10pm.
- OK.
- Hello, Leni.
- Hello my beauty.
Tonight you are the proud of Russia.
I'm presenting my niece, Dominik Egorova.
Dmitry Ustinov, a value trend to the art
If there is ever anything I can do
for you, don't hesitate me to ask.
May be we have a photo?
Yes
American!
American! don't shoot!
- American!
- On your knees!
Did you hear anything?
As far as we know, they got away clean.
They will be at your apartment
by now. Anything sensitive?
I know. No. Of course not.
OK, you fly to
DC in the morning.
It'll be a sting,
but we'll get you out.
It doesn’t look like anyone
was actually killed but...
Washington has questions.
So I got to ask.
What a fuck where you thinking?
I was protecting my ass
How that work out? He got away,
didn’t he?
Well, I guess you said it hear it for me
Those guys in the park...
the word is, they were vice cops,
and come for Chechnya dealers
as some family guy getting a
blow job in the bushes.
They weren't there for Marble.
They just got lucky.
The Chances are they were question to you,
and here we go.
But You can pay your ass they
are looking for now
They are expecting you, Deputy Director.
Thank you.
There are bold news about your niece.
I trust she is recovering?
She is in surgery now.
But... the prognosis for
her legs is not good.
Sorry to hear that. Drink?
It depends, what's the occasion?
I think you want one.
There was an incident Last night,
at Gorky Park.
Undercover Narcotics Agents saw
what they thought,
was a drug deal... and crosses,
when they mold in to question this man.
The other man fired his weapon.
Clearly attempt to distraction.
Now we know his name is Nate Nash.
He’s an official counselor
but he's a CIA.
He left the country this morning
on a diplomatic passport.
On the other...
the man he was meeting
does not panic, does not run.
He simply walks away.
My question is.
Who is he?
Your uncle Vanya has come
to visit the invalids.
You look well.
The Doctor said you wont
be able to walk for months.
Doctors don’t know everything.
No, They don’t.
I'll make some tea.
Let me help.
I'm glad my brother is in jail to
see what that clumsy fool did to you.
It would have broken his heart.
It was an accident.
Are you smoking?
I can smell it on you.
Why not?
I heard they already have ...a... have a
replacement for you at the company.
This girl named Sonja.
Obviously she is good.
Not as good as you, but
with time she can learn.
Have you read the reviews?
Competitive as you are.
Have you come to comesorate, uncle?
No, I have come to help.
Tell me, this apartment...
it belongs to Bolshoi, right?
How long you think they will
allow you to stay here
now they know you're not longer
a part of the company?
Three months? Six months?
If they are generous.
What about medical coverage
for your mother?
- They pay that as well, right?
- Yes.
Does she know?
She I’s not stupid.
Of course not.
And I know I haven't been around
as much since my brother died.
But... I'm here now.
And I want to help you.
So come see me when you're ready, please.
I have something for you.
You know, Dominika,
there are no accidents.
We create our own faith.
Sonja?
Hi.
How are you?
What is it?
I'm scared.
I went to see her at the hospital.
The way she looked at me. She knows...
She doesn't know.
What we have done is a sin.
They have always favored her.
No one else got the chance.
Is that fair? _
Isn't that a sin?
Good, I think it's enough for tonight.
Get some rest.
For 3 minutes.
There has been an accident
at the Bolshoi Theater.
Women's locker room. Please hurry.
Honey?
Mom?
Mama?
What... What happened?
Nobody there.
Where's Leni?
The Bolshoi said they wouldn't pay anymore.
I am going to take care of us.
You could have come to my office.
It's cold outside.
Not yet.
You broke her jaw.
You've always had a temper, haven’t you?
You said you could help us.
If you help me.
So... what do you want me to do?
National Security is interested in knowing
more about Dmitry Ustinov.
You met him at he Bolshoi.
Do you remember?
He likes you.
A broken bird that he could help.
Something is legal he
wont be able to resist.
So, in a few weeks,
when your leg is better,
I want you to get to know him.
And get close to him and win
his trust.
How do you propose I win his trust?
You always know how to put on a show.
Find someone else.
Have you ever seen
state on hospital?
Rats in the hallways.
Patients lying in their own waste.
If you do this, Dominika,
I will make sure, your mother
can keep her Doctors.
And I will make sure you can stay in
your apartment.
But only if I can show you,
can be a value to the state.
One night. That's all I'm asking.
Do this for your mother, Dominika.
He has dinner at the Hotel Andarja
every Friday at 9,
The car will arrive and you're a
part with to bring it to the hotel.
And you carry nothing with you.
We will arrange a room and
something for you to wear.
Make yourself presentable
Wear you hair the way you
wear at night at the Bolshoi
Let him see, just sit at the bar.
He sits at the same table
overlooking the restaurant.
You will stand out from the sort of
women who tend to go there.
I'm certain he will initiate contact.
And just do what he asks.
Ans when he drops his guard, I want you
to replace his phone with a duplicate
I'll make sure you're safe.
- A glass of Champagne. Please.
- Surely.
Dominika Egorova?
What a pleasure. May I join you?
Actually I am waiting for a friend.
Then I'll keep you company while you wait
Please.
Terrible what happened to you.
Just bad luck
I don't think you believe that
My father joint himself to death at the age
of 43 and left us with nothing.
Now I could buy this place
and anyone in it.
Is that luck?
Do you think anyone born in my
situation could have done this thing?
There is no such thing as luck.
Just like you being here.
There is no friend, is there?
Tell me the real reason you are here?
I came to see you.
And what is it you want from me?
All I ever wanted was to be a dancer.
Ever since I was a small child
now I take the bus to the
rehearsal after school
and I would look out the windows at
the people going about their lives
going to work, half-asleep,
and I will tell myself
I'm not like them,
and I never will be.
Because I'm special.
I want to be special again.
Beautiful room.
I'm surprised you can afford it.
Will you excuse me for just a moment.
Of course.
Can we be alone?
Take off your dress.
Come here.
Cracking the vase.
True value comes
from the smallest imperfection.
A refining detail
That's what makes it a worthy collection.
Slow down.
Slowly. Slow down.
No no!
Slowly!
Slowly
Hey... Hey, you!
How did this happen?
Ustinov dismissed the security
so I saw no opportunity, and they took it.
Why would he do that?
She asked him too.
She could be useful.
She is a witness.
Get rid of her.
I trust at discretion.
If I be you, I would be very sure.
With doubts?
Yes
shame.
You knew what would happen once I
got in that room, didn't you?
You wouldn't have gone if I told
you what would have to happen.
I wouldn't have a choice
You knew what I do.
You came to me. That was your choice.
You are my uncle.
I would never have let him hurt you.
He was inside me.
And I want to die.
You don't have to.
There is another life
for you if you want it.
You have potential, great potential.
You did well to get him alone
but what you said in that
bar was exactly right.
Because you told him exactly
what he needed to hear.
There is a program that can teach
you everything you need to know.
It's training is very hard.
Only a few make it.
You know how to survive.
That's why I chose you.
Unless I'm wrong.
Perhaps you don't like to have my word,
perhaps you disapprove.
In that case
your future will be out of my hands.
I'm sorry.
Good morning, Mama.
What is it?
I have to go away for a while.
Leni will come to stay.
Is this something that
your uncle arranged.
I'll take care of us now.
You don't have to do this.
It's too late for that now.
Oh, no. What have you done?
I'm sorry.
I warned you about him.
The way he looked at you as a child.
Oh... Mom.
I tried to keep him away.
I tried to protect you.
You hold something back.
Don't give him all of you.
That is how we survive.
Yes, Mama.
Welcome to the State School 4.
You will know me as major.
Inside you will find the name you will use
during the train.
Under no circumstances we will reveal
your true name,
or any personal information
to cadet or member of staff.
- Is that understood?
- Yes.
Good
I show you to your room.
You are not like our usual recruits.
Most of them come from the
Military with some training already.
You will have to work hard to catch up.
I will do as it is ask from me.
I am sure you will.
But someone like you does not enough here.
By choice....
Prima Ballerina who has an uncle in the SVR . [Foreign
Intelligence Service of the Russian Federation]
What is your crime?
Well, I suppose it doesn't matter
If you can not be of service to the state, I
am willing to pull a bullet through your head
The Cold War did not end
and shattered into a
thousand dangerous species
The Westerner grow weak.
Drunk on
shopping and social media.
Torn apart by hatred between the races
and as a result, the world is in chaos.
Only Russia
is willing to make the sacrifices
required for victory.
There to be peace, we must once again
we must please ourselves
at the head of nations.
From this day forward you will become
SPARROWS.
Weapons in a global struggle for power.
You have been selected for your beauty.
Because of your strength
and then, in some cases because
of your vulnerability.
Katya, Viktor, come here, please.
Here we deal with
psychological manipulation.
You will be trained to determine
a targets weakness,
to exploit that weakness
through deduction
and to extract information.
Take off your cloths.
Your body belongs to the state.
Since your birth, the state nourished it,
now the state asks something in return.
You have to learn to
sacrifice for a higher purpose.
To push yourself beyond
all the limitations.
And forget the sentimental morality
with which you have arisen.
Or is it pride?
In my experience, the proud
will be the first to fall.
Victor, take on your cloths.
They ready for you.
That is the recommendation on this panel
that you will be suspended indefinitely
from far assignment.
You'll be staying her in the States, Nate.
So... who is going to handle Marble?
That is no longer of your concern.
Simone,
I've been with this guy for 3 years.
He is not going to deal with
anybody that he doesn't know
and doesn't trust
like I said no longer your concern.
Gretel,
an invisible chemical compound
tailored to each subject.
Worn on the hands
after intimate contact.
The subject will be traceable
for up to 6 weeks.
Every human being is a puzzle of meat
You must learn to insured what is missing,
con man the missing piece
and they will give you anything.
This man is a diplomat at the Dutch Embassy
with access to NATO military planning.
6 years ago his marriage ended when the
police were called to his apartment
for the domestic disturbance
His wife accused him of improperly
touching their daughter.
Several nights a week he hires girls.
Runaways, addicts.
What does he want?
He wants something rough.
He goes to Runaways
because they ca not call the police.
- No.
- You disagree?
He wants a daughter, someone
to take care of ...and
he will pay for it.
Very good, Katya.
He never touches the girls.
He buy's them dinner.
Next...
This man representative Juvashia in Parliament, he was the leading
critic of the President until he was arrested for indecency.
He was a leading critic of
the President until
he was arrested for indecency
What did he want?
He looks like a degenerate
by degenerate you
mean, a homosexual?
Yes.
- correct, though
you're so judgmental
we all have our passions,
his happened to be around the young.
Anja, come here for a moment.
Here he is.
Give him what he wants.
What do you mean?
You called him degenerate?
Therefore, he doesn’t want what's
between your legs.
So... be a boy.
On your knees.
Not the first time, I'm sure
must have been a boy in
the field behind your house.
A girl on a rainy bus station?
We like to think it makes a difference.
But it doesn’t.
It's just flesh.
I can't!
Yes, you can.
Tomorrow you'll try again.
And again the day after that.
You must enjoy yourself to
what you find repellent
find beauty in the human delusion
that the pleasures of the flesh
will make us whole again.
Even when the subject is repellant,
the body can be tricked.
Increasing fingers to the thigh
brings blood to the groin.
Manipulation of the nipple
leads to arousal.
Audio used... trigger
sexual desire.
But Physical manipulation is not enough.
You must learn to love on command.
What is it to be loved?
To be seen.
To be recognized.
To feel no longer alone.
- When did you first notice the tail?
- Week ago
What do you make on that?
The Russians you still follow
me to follow me it means they
are looking for amazing Marvel
stone out there. It's a lie.
As far as we know.
You gotta talk to him to him.
Marble refused all attempts at communication
of the last four and a half months
you work 'em out for me.
I know you can't get me in a rush into of this,
somewhere close somewhere in Eastern Europe.
SVR be on me right away.
Marvel kept word he's going to surface.
Otherwise, this guarantee is,
he is gonna stay silence.
Simon, you gotta send me back.
Alright.
You got one assignment.
You can contact him,
and you convince him to
work with another Officer
That'll be me.
Will be coming with you.
Would you have a problem with that?
No, no problem.
These soldiers have been deployed
overseas for almost a year.
Welcome them home.
Turn off the lights.
No rush.
What's your name?
Pyotr.
Do you have somebody home?
Someone you think about
Close your eyes.
Think about a face
remember our smell
the ancient
Welcome Mr.Dantes
sweet, sentimental maintaining control
but you chose a boy, touche.
Your choose of boy, so you would
not have to give yourself
wont always be, as he see
next!
Three days ago, Nash was
reassigned to Budapest.
I believe it is an attempt to
re-establish contact with the 'mole'.
We have friends in Budapest.
And then pick him up and...
extract the
information directly.
That means we have to
explain the President
why every Officer we have in Western
Europe is snatched in retaliation.
Vanya is correct.
The President will not condone anything but
antagonizes the Americans unnecessarily
Not yet.
But your propose is when?
Nash is a skilled Officer,
that night, in the park
he made a mistake
he reacted emotionally
which tells me
he cares about the man
I propose we give him
someone else to care about
You are accused of assaulting a fellow.
He tried to rape me.
And your honor is worth to trying
Russia of a provincing contempt?
It was never my intention to
province Russia of anything.
And yet here we are.
Matron, what is your opinion?
Its only been three months,
but I believe Katya still
has potential.
I'd like to talk alone with the accused.
You did well with Ustinov in Moscow,
That's why you given this chance.
You where told what would happened
to you if your fail here?
Yes
so..why not let it happen?
I serve the state.
I serve our President.
I serve you, General.
But I owe him anything.
What sort of man would send his niece
to the State School Four?
A patriot.
My wife and I saw you dance once.
That was the different life.
There are so many.
Don't you fine?
You may go.
The sprouts must harden himself
against the weak and sentimental.
And see these things for what they are.
Selfishness.
Katya,
what does he want?
Come forward.
For the deception for being completely.
You must hold nothing back.
Nothing... understand?
Give him what he wants.
Well?
Turn around!
No!
I said, turn around.
Don't look at her.
I want to watch you do it.
Look at me!
Look at me.
I said, look at me.
Well?
What are you waiting for?
I'm ready.
Will you going to fuck me or not?
Nothing?
Shame.
Bitch!
Power.
That what he wants.
Get dressed.
There is a car waiting
to take you to Moscow.
I've done everything you asked of me.
Don't contrary
you have done nothing I asked.
But my superior think otherwise.
I suppose we will find out.
Good bye
Dominika
Hallo mama.
How are you?
I'm home.
My baby...
Hallo!
Yes
they will never let you go.
I will find a way.
Welcome home.
How are you?
Have a seat.
- What can I get you?
- I am not hungry.
Oh... Come on, you used to love this
place when you were little.
You've always been so serious with your
big grown-up eyes and your child's face.
What do you want, uncle?
There is a traitor hiding in
a place in the government.
Progeny one of the
intelligence agencies.
A mole
His last contacts...
...is an American now in Budapest.
What I want from you is
to get close to him.
And establish trust.
And then you bring me
the name of the mole.
You follow the trail whatever it needs.
You'll Sacrifice whatever
needs to be sacrificed.
Do you understand?
Yes, uncle.
This is for you.
What is it?
New passport. Credentials.
New name, Katerina Zubkova.
And what reward will they give you?
A promotion?
I understand you're angry with me.
You sent me to whore school.
I made you special again.
You have a gift, like me.
You see through people.
You see them for what they really are.
And you always stay one step ahead.
If you do this for me and I'll let you go,
if that's what you want?
But I feel you wont.
This is what you are meant to do.
Yes, uncle.
Let's eat.
Excuse me.
- Do you have everything?
- Yes sir.
How does that sound?
Welcome to Budapest.
You must be Katerina?
Hallo
You are pretty.
I'll show you to your room.
The bathroom is down the hall.
I'm I there, and you through there.
I keep my door locked. If I where
you I would do the same.
Stay out of my way and I stay out of yours
and we should get along file.
- Is that clear?
- Yes.
I imagine, tomorrow you
meet our station Chief
a Warning.
Chief Volontov never met an idea
he didn't want to take credit for
and..he likes to try with the new girls
when he is not drooling after strippers
He is going to like you
Tell me about the American.
He is not exactly a match fit
he swim’s every afternoon.
Works his time but...
he drinks to much
he looks at pornography.
Nothing out of the ordinary
Anal, threesomes...
Usually two man on a girl.
No relationships to speak of
a few girls he has paid..couple
of times, but then he
Feels guilty and gives them tips.
Perhaps with the more successive
we knew what we were looking for.
I am offering completely
cooperation of my office.
And in exchange I hope to cuelt love
cube us in form of your progress.
Of course.
You need a hand?
No, it's all right.
You wanted to be good?
Let me help you.
Come on, give it to me.
Every women being is a puzzle of meat.
Learn how to meet missing piece, and
they will give you everything.
You thought you were the only one?
We'll always be their whores.
Unless, of course, we
have something they want.
If I where you I'd find something.
The pool is open from 6 in the morning
until 10 at night, from Monday to Friday.
From six to eight on weekends.
No personal belongings are allowed.
I made a mistake, sorry.
Handing your membership card here
for a local key.
You get your card back
when you return the key.
Any questions?
No.
[speaking Russian]
How did you know I was a Russian?
It was just a guess.
You speak well.
I used to live in Moscow.
Do you miss it?
Yeah... you know... food and people.
What are you doing in Budapest?
I'm a translator at the Embassy. You?
Commercial counselor. Medical supplies.
I've never seen you at any of the
Embassy events.
I haven't been here long.
Excuse me.
Blonde suits you better way.
Have we met?
I thought I saw you at the pool
yesterday and on the tram, I think.
You are mistaken.
Would you like to get
something to eat with me?
I know a Turkish place at the station.
A shit hole, but the food is pretty good.
Maybe you know it.
I am not hungry.
Perhaps another time.
See you in the pool. I guess.
Your ID is missing.
Are you sure?
Put it down my self.
Sorry, I'll have to make you a new one.
I've got your picture on file.
Take your time.
She came in under
the name of Katerina Zubkova.
Registered as a translator for the Embassy.
But her real name is Dominika Egorova.
She use to dance with the Bolshoi.
There is officially no record
of her being SVR.
But that's bullshit.
She is here for Marble. And now...
- stay away from her.
- I think she is valuable.
- And now you think she is recruitable?
- Maybe.
OK... that is not what you here for.
Just keep doing what you doing
Play dead.
Let's take a sleep and pray
Marble sticks here again...
so we can get him back into place.
That's the priority.
She is Ivan Egovars niece.
Deputy Director of the SVR?
I have nieces.
Spend most of their times exposing
themselves on the internet
Why would she use her real name?
Because she is an innocent.
Or because it is a provocation
Both of witch are very good
reasons to stay away from her.
There is something about this girl.
She is gold.
- I know it.
- OK.
See what you can find out.
- Thanks.
- Just go slow, okay?
- Nate!
- Ahm?
If she does let you fuck her,
she is definitely SVR...
because she is way out of your league.
I need you to get me on a list for
an event at the American Embassy.
I can do that.
- Thank you.
- If...
you give me a progress report in return
I established contact.
Contact?
I thought you'd be on your back by now?
You know...
There are always stories about Sparrows.
Capable of performing
tricks on a man's mind.
Not to mention the rest of the body.
A magic pussy.
That's what they say.
Perhaps I'll find out.
Just a little fun.
But the offer stands. If you need
help, Don't hesitate to ask.
After all, everyone needs a friend.
The success of these efforts
will be critical... for securing
Hungary economy and ties with
its neighbors.
This is clearly the moment of
rapid change in the world.
Making it imperative for each
region to stay competitive.
Thanks to the Hungarian President
for hosting us
and the American Ambassador
to organize this.
Finally, I would like to thank my
Chief of Staff, Stephanie Boucher..
Without her hard work
we would not be here tonight.
Stephanie.
Dominika Egorova.
You know my name?
You told me.
You stole my ID from the pool.
That would be illegal.
Where you just looking for me?
I know where to find you. If I was.
I'm curious, Did you want me
to know you were following me,
or are you just real clumsy?
You Americans always think the rest of
us is so interested in you, don't you.
What made you wanna become a translator?
I'm sure if you know my name you
found out other things about me,
I have wondered what it would be like
to pursue something your hole life,
and then have it ripped away from me.
What is it like?
How does it make you feel?
It doesn't matter.
My mother is unwell. If I work for the
government that still helps to take care of her.
My uncle helped me to get the job.
Your uncle is a very powerful man.
In my country if you don't matter to
the man in power, you don't matter.
Is that so different in your country?
It supposed to be, but...
Are you a patriot?
No.
Then why do you do what you do?
Better than selling car tires
Have you ever sold tires?
No.
Then you can not, can't you?
Good point.
Hey..ah..I would like to see you again.
Why? Are we going to become friends?
Is that what you want?
I don't have any.
There is a Russian restaurant
right by the opera.
Have dinner with me there.
Tomorrow at 8pm
Marta?
Senator Chief of Staff.
SWAN
Initial Payment $ 250,000?
Are you home?
That was him at the Embassy?
It was
playing hard to get, hurry up.
No substitute for a good, old-fashioned
blow job, in my experience.
He is not like that.
What is this?
A copy of the report that
Volontov sent to Moscow, three days ago.
Apparently you have made an enemy.
Good evening.
Good evening, sir.
Is this a coincidence?
You were right. I do need a friend.
Everyone needs a friend.
I need you to send a
report that you are
impressed about my progress
I've made with Nash.
I need more time.
And then, I would owe you.
How do I know that you
are paying your debts?
You're right about Sparrows.
We are special.
Do you know what they teach us?
How to determine what a lover needs..
And I knew what you needed from
the first time I ever saw you
Someone who does not laugh
at your microscopic dick.
Get your hands off me!
Take a look at the camera
over my left shoulder.
Tomorrow you write a favorable report,
or I let you arrest for sexual assault.
You will be recalled to Moscow
and your career will be over.
Good night.
Hallo!
This is an automated test of your digital
phone line. Sorry for the interruption.
Alpha, Charlie, Zero, Whiskey.
Vienna.
This is Dominika.
Come on up.
- Hey.
- Can I have a drink?
Come on in.
Whiskey?
Thank you.
So... you wanna tell me what happened?
My big boss's boss is insulted that I
don't want to sleep with him.
What is his name?
Maxim Volontov.
- I've heard from him.
How did you know where I lived?
Why did you leave Russia?
I screwed up at work.
Why would a CIA Officer fire
his gun in a public park?
I did it for a friend.
Because I knew what
they would do to him.
So do you.
What do you want, Dominik?
I think you should rather
go home and figure it out.
See you tomorrow.
You know where you'll find me.
Katerina, are you changed your hair?
I'll leave you.
Nice to meet you.
Would you prefer a drink?
Sure, but I don't have much time.
I did not know you would coming.
On what occasion?
Do I need one?
I'm on my way to Vienna, for a meeting
and I thought I do visit you.
- What happened to your eye?
- I bumped it into the pool.
Do you have any news about
our American friends?
He become to lose his guard around me.
He told me about what happened at the
park after I established trust.
- So... how was he?
- A memorable.
- But he's handsome, right?
- Is he?
Is there anything out of the ordinary that
you would like to report?
If you lose contact...
or if he goes missing for a day or more...
you need to let me know, because our
superiors getting impatient.
I have something for you.
Something new.
A case with great potential.
I thought I made it very clear
you only have one mission.
A Russian agent inside the American
government is always of value, is it not?
Marta and I are developing
the asset together.
A Senator, Chief of Staff.
And she is willing to cooperate?
She is compromised, she has no choice.
- When will you see her again?
- In London.
In a weeks time. But we need more money.
Your blackmail will not be enough
to establish a long-term exchange.
What do you have in mind?
$ 250,000.
That's a lot of money.
Buy you can get it.
I have to leave.
- Oh... I forgot my coat.
- I'll get it.
Thank you.
I have waited a lifetime
for something like Swan.
I've worked a year developing her.
- She is not your's to trade.
- Now you have the money to make the exchange.
I'll make sure you get the credit.
I just need more time. Please.
- What do they have on you?
- I saw something that I not supposed to.
What, did you see?
You will not get swan for free.
I was there the night they
killed Dmitri Ustinov.
They where telling
me to cut my throat.
Will you help me?
I don't have a fucking choice.
What would you give me,
if I told you how to get rid of Katerina?
What do you want?
Oh..am I too late?
Sorry, we're closed. You can come
again tomorrow morning. We open at 9.
I am not going to be here tomorrow.
Is there any way you can make an exception?
Please. I wanted to open an
account for a family member.
In case anything happens to me.
I can't let you in.
Maybe you could take the form,
and I could buy you a coffee and
we could fill them out together?
Do you have a passport and
you know all the information?
- Yes, I have everything.
- OK.
- Excellent.
- Thank you.
Marta?
Have you ever been to a farm?
That’s what it smells like
when you butcher an animal.
I took my time with her.
So you would see what happens
when you tell the secrets.
Please, please.
This is your only warning.
Now,
call the police!
Where the fuck have you been?
Close the door.
Marble surfaced.
Jesus Christ. Here?
In Vienna.
You don't say anything?
What is that?
It's a warning,
She is a sparrow.
I told you she is way out of your league.
I think she's still recruitable.
Now that we know what we are dealing,
maybe we can do more so.
She is a Sparrow we can't trust a fuck,
no word that comes out of her mouth
Yeah?
When?
And you came home to
find out how I did this?
Yes
This was not just a break in.
This was torture. A punishment.
Any idea why someone would do this to her?
What happened to your eye?
Did you get along with her?
- You're upset.
- Of course I'm fucking upset!
You know something, don't you?
Whoever it is your shielding...
whoever you are scared of...
- we can protect you.
- May I go?
I'm assuming that you
guys were pretty close.
He must be pretty scared.
For yourself.
When I was in Moscow, they talked about
a program that Khrushchev had set up.
Young Officers trained to
seduce and manipulate.
They called them Sparrows.
That is what you are, that is right?
The thing I just can not wrap my
hair around is, why a man would
put his niece trough something like that?
I was told to take a man to a hotel.
To get information.
They said he was an enemy of the state.
And in exchange my mother would
get the Doctor she needed.
Instead, they cut his throat.
He died on top of me.
There could be no witnesses,
so my uncle gave me a choice.
Die...
or become a Sparrow.
What they did to Marta was a message.
They cut her open to show me what they will
do to me if I don't give them what they want.
- What do they want?
- A name.
They think you're an agent.
What do you think?
I don't care.
I just want my mother to be safe.
The man that you work for,
man like your uncle,
they never let you go, no
matter what you getting.
This is how they function.
You only matter because of what you can do,
for me don't exist
unless they say so.
And that's just now, I mean...
when you where dancing
you dancing for them.
Because they where letting you.
You can see it now, right?
You belong to them, pretty much your life.
So... Dominika, work with me.
Make this something you own, for the
first time in your life.
Make them fucking pay.
What is it do you want from me?
Whatever you can give us.
But if I have my choice,
access to your uncle.
Be your spy?
Is it?
Is that any different from being his spy?
Yes, because I would never
ask you to do what he did.
Nothing is worth that.
I need to sleep.
Why don't you take my room.
You asked me why I fired a gun in Moscow.
The man I was protecting
had everything to lose.
He was benefiting from the system,
but when he saw what was
happening in his name...
He didn’t just say that he didn't know.
He risked his life. He risked everything.
He didn't deserve to die
in a cellar somewhere.
If you do this...
I will do everything in
my power to protect you.
Can I trust you?
I promise, you can.
Wait, wait, don't.
Thank you.
I danced my first solo to this.
It's Grieg.
I was so nervous the night
before,
I couldn't sleep.
And I played this music in my
room and...
and...
after I felt asleep I dreamed that...
the music was color... and I could
and I could paint it on all
the audiences
faces with my hands.
I'm sorry about what happened to you.
I'm really pretty glad that you're here.
Me too.
Are you sure about this?
Alright. Listen,
This is what I want you to do.
Go back to your normal routine.
Go in to work and write
a report, about me.
About the time we spent
and how close we became.
Say that I am a
fool and you've got me on a hook.
Write that I am ambitious,
and that I drink.
And then I ask him to prove to my father...
on which means, I will make a mistake.
Then I need you to go home.
The police will be finish
with the apartment by this evening.
And then just wait for my signal.
Hallo!
I'm going to ask you some routine
questions to begin.
Name?
Dominika Egorova.
- Did you eat breakfast this morning?
- Yes.
Are you an Officer of the
Russian Intelligence Service?
Yes.
Are you here because CIA,
whoever named Nate Nash, recruited you?
Yes.
Are you willing to work
for the American government?
Yes.
And you intend to give
us genuine information?
Yes or no?
Yes.
Why would you do that?
I thought it was just yes or no.
I'm just curious.
I know the nature from the men I work for.
Why do you work for them?
They gave me no choice.
I have a question .. You
You only spike when Nate's name comes up.
- Did you engaged in sexual intercourse with him?
- Hey, that's...
- Take it easy.
- That's what you do, right?
- Marty.
- What you are trained for.
- Did anyone tell you...
anybody ever told you that..
- Why do you want to know that, Bratok?
Big Brother?
Please answer the question.
We need to know if you're
emotionally involved.
The answer is no.
So..are you satisfied?
- Yeah.
- If I'm going to work for you,
you need to transfer money
to my bank account in Vienna.
$ 30,000 to start with.
I don't know what you an Nate
discussed,
but I think we are getting a
little ahead of our self sweetheart to.
See what you brought us.
If it's significant...
what about the Senators Chief of Staff?
Excuse me?
A Chief of Staff run by the SVR?
She agreed to sell information
on a Satellite Defense System.
I fly to London on Friday to meet with her.
Shall I provide you with
the account information?
Here she is.
It's to the left.
Look... here we go.
What are you doing here?
I thought you might need some help
after what happened to poor Marta.
Of course, you're lucky
not to be harmed yourself.
I appreciate your concern.
So I do wonder how Swan would react
if she see me with you?
Do you really want to be the
multiple of this whole operation?
Director Egorova would be very displeased.
Go upstairs, Room 624.
I'll call you if I need you.
Go.
- Who the hell is that?
- He's gotta a key.
Did you see anybody else
was going in that room?
No, I think that's... Yes, it's Volontov.
That’s her boss.
Vodka.
- Do I know you?
- We have a friend in common.
Where is she?
Unfortunately, Marta wasn't able
to make it, so... she sent me.
Hm...
I was just leaving.
Do you think I care about
people who I meeting with?
I think in this case you might.
Marta is a well-known intelligence Officer.
When photographs of your
relationship going public,
you lose your security
clearance and your job.
But I don't think that any of that is
necessary. You're here for business, as am I.
$ 250,000 was a figured
that you agreed upon.
Your daughters tuition
payments are coming out.
I believe your ex-husband
is about to lose another job.
Don't you think you'd be
more comfortable in the private room?
Where did they find you?
Follow me.
- You are out here with him?
- Yes.
Let's get the show on the road.
Is this Colonel Maxim Volontov?
He is the Chief of the
Budapest resident area.
A real drink, would you Boris?
Let's get done with it.
You heard her. Make her a drink.
So...
shall we proceed?
I just wanna be a clear.
I am here strictly explorigly matter.
As long as what you have to offer is a value,
I am sure we will have no difficulties.
I am a Chief of Staff to
a United States Senator.
The last person had
my job headed to the
the fucking CIA, being
in the room with me.
Fucking value.
I think she is drunk.
- You think?
And I'm sure that if you
are as important as
you say, you don't
want to waste any time.
So...
do you have anything to sell?
I have the first set of disks with me.
Today.
I just wanna make clear that
I'm not doing this because
I am..a..ideologist or pacifist
or something, you know.
Where are the discs, Stephanie?
Where is my money?
$ 250,000 for delivery, as agreed.
Yeap!
Sorry.
I just need to authenticate them.
Why don't you give me a real pour, Boris?
Why don’t you get it yourself?
Everything alright?
Everything OK?
I just have to wait for them to load.
Tell me, Boris?
You got a little babushka back in Moscow?
Of course you do.
It never seizes to amaze me.
Why are all Russian women so sexy?
All the men look like turds.
No, no, no, don't.
- Where you going?
- I will go to buy her some more time.
- Why does it take so long?
- Just one more minute.
What a fuck is that...?
Just checking. Is everything
all right with your room, Sir?
Fine.
- Shall I check the minibar?
- There is no need.
Sorry to disturb you.
It's finished.
Everything seems to be in order.
One more minute longer,
I'm going to shoot her.
Did she get her?
She did.
Nice accent.
I will leave now.
You wait an hour and then you go.
Will be in touch for the next delivery.
Sure thing.
Fuck it!
Oh, oh... she took the money.
She took the money.
There he go.
We will get the discs and take
them back to the field office.
I follow as soon as I
get that squared away.
Make the necessary arrangements.
Change of plans.
We go directly to Heathrow.
Moscow wants to congratulate us in person.
I'll call the Director Egorova.
No need.
Director Egorova gave the order himself.
The disks and your passport.
Turn the car around.
Yeah?
Boucher is dead.
What are you talking about?
Our guys outside went
after the money too early.
She panicked.
Stepped in front of a fucking truck.
What a fuck!
You think they had somebody in the hotel?
- How would if.
If they think she tipped
us off, they would have kill her.
And Nate, the till car changed direction.
Looks like they headed to Heathrow.
Fuck, Trish! We fucked her real.
Fucked her!
You look nervous.
They entering Terminal 2.
Looks like Aeroflot.
This is a boarding announcement .
British European Airways flight 422
to Amsterdam .
Will begin boarding shortly.
All passengers please proceed to Gate B-42.
Passport?
Enjoy your flight.
Damned!
I always had my doubts about her.
She is my niece.
What?
My brother's daughter.
Give me the discs, please.
Of course.
Thank you. Take him away.
Did you give Mrs. Boucher to Americans?
No.
Who did?
I don't know.
You can start.
Let's start again.
Did you give Boucher to Americans?
No.
Are you working for the Americans?
I love my country.
You gave Boucher to Americans.
For money?
Or for the handsome American?
No.
Did you tell the Americans about Boucher?
The last time.
No.
Did you give Boucher to Americans?
Please.
Please stop.
You made a mistake.
It's not your fault.
You have to tell them
what they want to know.
Please.
I can only protect you
if you tell the truth.
The truth?
There is no other mission than this one.
Follow the trail wherever it leads.
Sacrifice whatever has to be sacrificed.
If they have my real name,
If they have a swan,
if you torture me,
they will trust me.
How could they don't.
You will not give up now.
Send me back.
Let me finish what we started.
Did they do well uncle?
And I?
Oh, my child.
What happened to you?
I was questioned by security services.
But they let you go?
Of course I'm innocent.
Chief Zakharov expects
you, Deputy Director.
The President is furious
about the loss of Boucher.
The mole would have got her anyway.
Now we get something in return.
His patience with your
niece is growing thin.
The Americans will trust her.
So.. you saying.
I think Dominika had her chance.
It is my opinion, she has developed
feelings for the American.
She has made a fool of you, Ivan.
Send her back to Nash.
Let Matorin shadow her.
If she is compromised he will find out.
The Americans will respond.
Nothing that we can not handle.
And what of Dominika?
Let her leash to her uncle.
Shall we tell the President
you priority ties to the safety of
the safety of your niece or the mission?
If she is compromised,
I promise she will be eliminated.
Thank you, Ivan.
You're welcome, Chief Zakharov.
Enjoy your night.
I'd ask you how you could in but
this is what we've taught you, isn't it?
Did they grant my request?
Yes, they did.
You're right.
I'm like you, uncle.
Oh, God!
Oh, thank God.
You know what this looks like, right?
They just let you go. Why would they do it?
Because I told them
that you would trust me now.
Enough to give me the name of the mole.
But you know I can't do that.
Of course I do.
So what next then?
I want to go to America.
Where I can be safe. Please.
- Alright.
- And my mother?
It will take some time, but
we can't get around, yeah?
And the money I was promised?
You'll get it. $ 30,000
in a bank in Vienna.
We couldn’t release payment
while you are in custody.
It is not enough.
How much do you want?
I need $ 250,000,
for resettlement.
OK.
You are helping me
with no, obvious advantages.
That is not what I expected.
If I hadn't waved you away at the
airport, what would you have done?
I would have kill them for you.
Nate?
Do you know what this is?
They use it for skin grafting.
Burning victims,
the blades so fine, you barely bleed
Do you know how long it takes to
peel the skin from a human being?
Hours. Even if you are good at it.
And I, I take my time with it.
Layer by layer.
Until I see the white
of the bone.
You know what we want to know...
but they wont stop until long after
you ready to talk.
If you pass out, I will inject
with a stimulate.
You will stay conscious
until we finished.
What's the name, Nate?
What's the name?
No?
Do you want more?
No, please.
So, we go deeper.
No!
No?
Come on, Nate, the name?
What's the name?
No?
Give it to me. Let me try.
Wait, wait.
Oh, God!
No?
Nate.
Nate?
Call the Embassy. The Embassy.
It was you who killed Matorin, wasn't it?
I can explain.
I'm sure you can.
My wife had dreamed about
becoming a dancer.
Long before I met her.
Of course, she was nothing on you, but she
used to dance for me in our living room.
When she felt ill
the Russian Embassy in New York refused...
to let an American Doctor operate on her.
Some... pity bureaucrats I offended,
sentenced her to death.
What passes for power.
I know you gave the Americans Boucher.
Only so that they would trust me.
And now we have to trust you?
I was born three days after
Stalin has led in state.
My father fought for him during the war.
He was party member.
We got privileges.
It took me few years to realize
I've been born in a prison.
Prisons makes a beast out of a man.
I learned to cheat, to lie,
to others before they do to me
to survive
by any means
so I had to decide,
Die in the prison where I was
born
or choose another side,
our clumsy American friends,
for whom individual freedom
is at least an inspiration.
So now, you know. I'm the mole.
I am the man you're looking for.
You are free to hand me over to your uncle.
You can give those people what they want.
Of course, there is another path.
What would that be?
After you turn me in, you will be a hero
beyond suspicion.
The ideal position to take my place
and continue my work with the Americans.
May your uncle and his kind pay for what
they've done to our country.
They will kill you.
Something will slice us all.
You have the power to decide
whether or not I die in vain.
You are better in this than any others.
This is the only way for you
to return to your mother.
You sent Matorin, didn't you?
So I wouldn't have a choice.
So that you would see.
You never did.
Hallo!
Hi...
Stop.
Face the wall.
I want to speak with the
Russian Ambassador.
My name is Mikhail Sergev.
I am an Ambassador here in Budapest.
Unfortunately, the Hungarians
are reviewing the diplomatic immunity.
Call Zakharov.
Tell him, I have what he wants.
I have the name of the mole.
Why wouldn't you tell me?
And I'll pass it a long.
Listen to me very carefully.
You're an arrant boy. I have an arrant.
You call Zakharov.
You will tell him to make a trade.
Me for the mole.
Once if that is arranged, I will
give the name to Zakharov personally.
Do this right, mister Ambassador?
And I might tell them
that this was your idea.
I'll see what I can do.
Thank you, Director Zakharov.
Speak of this to no one else.
Yes sir.
No loose ends.
Nothing that can lacks
back to the President.
And the girl?
You can uncuff her
All right, this is, how this is gonna go.
They will escort you part of the way.
Once you confirmed the identity of
our mole, you're going on alone.
You passes the mid point.
Don't exchange words, don't look back.
If anything goes wrong, we abort.
If you try to run, we are
authorized to shoot.
We will not hesitate, you understand?
All right, Nate, it's time.
Your uncle will be very proud.
He might be.
Are you going to tell me how
you found out his name?
Is it going to make a difference?
There is an investigation.
They think it's me.
I guess that was the playing all along?
Stop here.
I got him back for you.
Do you think they just let him
make it a cross over a life?
You realize you might have just
earned to get killed?
I think one day you'll understand.
No, I don't think I will.
Some things can't be sacrificed.
We don't throw people away.
Show us his face!
What the hell is going on?
Why is there a delay?
Confirm the identity of your agent
That's our man!
She fucked them.
Goodbye, Nate.
Good morning.
Please, sit.
You were right about the niece.
She did very well.
She called from Budapest.
Gave us the name of the mole.
Wonderful news.
There was this security detail,
search the mole's office
his apartment.
The apartment was covered
in bullets
attributed to Nash.
This is a statement
for an account opened in a
private bank in Vienna
into which Americans have recently
made payments of $250,000.
A lot of Money paid to a defector.
The account is in your and
your passport number.
- Oh,..I forgot my coat.
- I'll get it.
You recently made a trip
to Vienna, did you not?
You know, this is my niece's written.
She's angry with me.
This is one of the disks,
Boucher gave us.
The disks you passed on to the President
Your personal victory.
It suppose to come from the DOD.
But at the request of your niece,
we examined it more closely.
The encryption signature suggests
it was written in Langley.
It's a fake.
You are special. You have a gift like me.
You see through people.
You see them for what they really are.
And you always stay one step ahead.
Great family I have
you killed me.
Didn't I do well, uncle?
The target is in reach.
Hallo!
captions: fayouSubs